Christian Gabriel Gill Desia

Phone: +549 343 4296247

Email: gillchristiang@gmail.com

LinkedIn Profile: ar.linkedin.com/in/gillchristian

Github account: gillchristian
Web: gillchristian.github.io

Skype: gill.christian2

Address: Urquiza 2714 Depto. C Piso 4, Santa Fe Capital, Santa Fe, Argentina.

Letter

My name is Christian. I am from Argentina. I studied Bioengineering for three years before changing my degree to CS at the <u>UTN</u>, Universidad Tecnologica Nacional (National Technological University).

I work as a full time front end developer at <u>4rsoluciones.com</u>. I work mostly doing custom WordPress themes development and AngularJS applications.

Before I worked freelance also doing front end development on WordPress themes.

Personally I have invested plenty of time on improving my knowledge and skills on the web languages and frameworks. Some of it can can be found at my Github account.

- WordPress helper classes to leverage Custom Post Types and Taxonomies register.
- Node.js simple API example.
- AngularJS directives for handling forms. I haven't been able to further develop this one.
- Starter front end project with Gulp tasks.
- Twitter like app with Angular and PHP. I developed it a while a go, when learning Angular.
- Clash army calculator. On the process of being refactored.

I haven't made contributions to OpenSource projects, besides some grammar corrections. But I like to keep a close eye on the projects I daily use. Such as: Angular 1 and 2, WordPress, CMB2, jQuery, slick slider, node.js. The list is actually quite large.

I really like to innovate and learn new things everyday to keep my skills up to date to the development world, and also find better ways to do what I already know.

I am eager to learn and improve as I overcome challenges. I will put my 140% to be up to the expectations you have for the position.

Job goals

Target areas

Web Development.

Target Industries

Web development, Internet, Media, Technology, Telecommunications, NGOs, Education.

Time availability

Saturdays not available.

Experience

07.2015 - today | 4r Soluciones, Santa Fe, Argentina

Front-end development.

Custom WordPress theme development. Single page application development with AngularJS.

03.2014 - 01.2015 | ADRA, NGO, Kyrgyzstan.

Public Relations on Internet. Web Developing.

Volunteering through Universidad Adventista del Plata (Entre Ríos, Argentina). Working on the web presence of the ADRA office: Facebook, Twitter and WordPress website. Assisting in project implementation.

03.2013 - 11.2013 | **Province of Entre Ríos Government**, Argentina. Education.

Work Area Risks Teacher. Teaching Work Area Risks in the course "Jovenes con más y mejor trabajo" (Youths with more and better work).

04.2012 - 12.2012 | **Province of Entre Ríos Government**, Argentina. Education.

English Teacher. Teaching English on a night school.

01.2010 - 12.2010 | Da'Vita Foods, Maryland, Estados Unidos. Industria.

Industrial bakery field employee. Industrial machinery multitasking: product packaging (bread and tortillas), stock keeping, driving forklift.

12.2007 - 03.2008 y 12.2012-03.2013 | Servicio Educacional Hogar y Salud (Home and Health

Educational Service), Villa Mercedes, San Luis, Argentina y Quillota, Chile, respectively. Preventive

health care books selling.

University health assistant. Preventive health talks house by house, in shops, businesses and public

entities, linked with the selling of health books.

1.2007 and 6.2011 | Córdoba, Argentina. Masonry.

Builder assistant.

Education

02.2015 - Present | Universidad Tecnológica Nacional, Santa Fe, Argentina. Computer Science.

Information Systems Engineer, In progress, University Degree. Approved classes: 8. Total classes: 36.

02.2011 - 12.2013 | Universidad Nacional de Entre Ríos, Argentina. Bioengineering.

Bioengineer, Abandoned, University Degree. Approved classes: 13. Total classes: 52.

Took three years and decide to change degree for Computer Science.

03.2007 - 12.2009 | Instituto Adventista Balcarce, Argentina. High School.

Skills

Databases.

SQL: mySQL. *Intermediate*

Web development.

Templating languages: HTML5, Jade.

Advanced

Stylesheet languages:

CSS3, SASS, Less, PostCSS. Advanced

Web programing languages: PHP, JavaScript. Advanced

JavaScript ES6, TypeScript. Intermediate

Frameworks, libraries, platforms:

WordPress, jQuery, AngularJS, Bootstrap. Advanced

Node.js, Express.js, Foundation. Intermediate

React, Angular2. Beginner

Task runners, package managers, others:

Gulp, Grunt, npm, Bower, jspm, Yeoman, slush, Composer.

Version control:

Git. Intermediate

Design tools

Adobe PhotoShop & Illustrator.

Beginner

Applications development.

Web & mobile frameworks: ionic.

Basic

Programing.

Object Oriented Programing: C++.

Basic

Office tools.

Presentations: Powerpoint, Google Slides, slides.com.

Documents: Word, Google Docs. Spreadsheets: Excel, Google Sheets.

Advanced

Operating Systems.

Windows: Advanced

Linux (mostly Ubuntu): Intermediate

Languages

Spanish.

Mother language.

English.

Speech: Advanced. Writing: Advanced. Reading: Bilingual. Last time used: present.

Russian.

Speech: Basic. Writing: Basic. Reading: Basic. Last time used: present.